Guide to Bowdoin College Catalogs, etc. Cubb.00215
Cubberley Education Library
Bowdoin College
1830-1987
Cubberley Education Library
Cubb.00215
228 item(s) Catalogs for 1830, 1839, 1851, 1859,1865, 1865/66-1870/71, 1872, 1873/74-1879/80, 1881/82-1884/85, 1886/87-1927/28, 1929/30-1942/43, 1944/45, 1946/47-1950/51, 1953/54, 1955/56, 1957/58, 1960/61-1962/63, 1964/65, 1966/67, 1972/73, 1975/76-1977/78
Located in Brunswick, Maine. Chartered in 1794. Established Medical School in 1820 which closed in 1921. Became coeducational in 1971.
Maine
- Named Professorships at Bowdoin College, 1976; 1 item(s) Information about named professorships and those who held them
- Bowdoin College: Medical Department, 1914-1915; 1 item(s) Catalog for 1914/1915
  Medical colleges
- Report of the President of Bowdoin College, 1891-1987; 89 item(s) Reports for 1891/92-1903/04, 1905/06-1938/39, 1940/41-1958/59, 1960/61-1970/71, 1973/74-1977/78, 1981/82-1987
- Report of the Finance Committe of Bowdoin College ( and the Treasurer), 1898-1930; 26 item(s) Reports for 1898-1899, 1901, 1903, 1905-1907, 1911-1926, 1929-1930
- Bowdoin College Regulations, 1890; 1 item(s) Bound with President's Reports
- Charter of Bowdoin College and Other Documents, 1876; 1 item(s) Bound with President's Reports
- Bowdoin in the War, 1867; 1 item(s) Bound with President's Reports--a list of all graduates and undergraduates involved in the Civil War
- Additions and Corrections to History of Bowdoin College, 1887; 1 item(s) Bound with President's Reports
- Addresses at the Inauguration of President Hyde, Bowdoin College, June 23, 1886, 1 item(s) Bound with President's Reports
- Three Discourses upon the Religious History of Bowdoin College, 1858; 1 item(s) Bound with President's Reports
- Longfellow Memorial Address, before the Alumni of Bowdoin College by Rev. Daniel R. Goodwin, July 12, 1882; 1 item(s) Bound with President's Reports
- Address on the Life and Character of Thomas C. Uphan, D.D., Late Professor of Mental and Moral Philosophy in Bowdoin College by Alpheus S Packard, 1873; 1 item(s) Bound with President's Reports
- Alpheus Spring Packard: A Commemorative Address before the Alumni Association of Bowdoin College, 1885; 1 item(s) Bound with President's Reports
- Obituary Record of the Graduates of Bowdoin College and the Medical School of Maine, 1898-1899; 3 item(s) Bound with President's Reports. Reports for years ending June 1898 and June 1899. List for decade ending June 1899